Good morning, Jay and the Stan team.
I'd like to enter my application for Launchpad.
My name is Sathian Srikrishnan. I am 43 years old
and a startup founder of Tooth Fairy Network,
where we turn a child's lost tooth into their first digital wallet.
I built this product for my own children.
I'm a divorced dad of two children,
and I stumbled upon this idea through the natural course of life.
I was a bit reluctant to even think and try this,
but I've been coming to a few of the Stan events
and been pretty impressed with the team, the people,
and the way you approach things.
And so I think this will be a wonderful learning opportunity.
I will be entering as a solo founder,
and I'm using AI as my co-founder.
I have a prototype and product
that's been clunky, that I'm revising daily,
and the current iteration I think genuinely has a chance of doing well.
I'm pretty good with people, and I'm pretty open-minded, guys,
so I think I will learn a lot from the other young founders
and people at this retreat, workshop.
So I think I want to give it a shot.
It is definitely out of my comfort zone.
I'm pretty sure I'll be the oldest person there,
but I think that's what learning and growth requires.
So I hope this intro video suffices
with a little bit of information.
You can visit my product at toothfairy.network.
There's a couple of big changes coming to the platform as well.
Like all products, it's constantly evolving.
And I appreciate your time and consideration
and look forward to your response. Thank you.